module.exports = [
    {
        "question": "2 + 3 = 5",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 3 = 3.2",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 1 = 6",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 1 = 9",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 7 = 64",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 3 = 21",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 4 = 72",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 2 = 3.5",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 2 = 2",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 1 = 10",
        "answer": true
    },
];
